No!
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Don't you do it.
Don't you fuckin' do it.
You're not dyin' here.
Not yet.
I never learned it.
Whatever tongue Ford saw fit to give ya.
I remember you.
If you're just gonna let me die now,
you could've kept ridin'.
There's the baby doll.
And the mama doll. And...
What's this?
The ghost gave it to me.
He said it's a warning.
He said he'll be watching us.
Just hang on.
Hang on, OK?
Hey. No. No more corpses up
here. Take her to cold storage.
- She doesn't belong down there.
- Then leave her in the hall!
We got 50 hosts in the
queue for analysis here.
Everything else goes in the dumpster.
You'll want to check her code.
She's the madame from the Mariposa.
- Yeah? Good for her.
- No. No. She...
I was just out with her in the park.
And you chose to bring her up here?
Are you aware that they all
just tried to incinerate us?!
She can control the other
hosts with her fucking mind!
Just... check her data stream.
You can't let her die.
Clear this out.
Get me a scalpel. And
lock this place down.
Are you afraid of me?
He can't hurt you.
What's his problem?
He get bored with his exquisitely
dull, pastoral existence?
I guess that was just for beta.
They want something more
exciting for the grand opening.
Like a little more bloodshed?
Ford wants a total narrative redesign.
You kidding?
All new dialogue trees?
Eh, they want a strong-but-silent type.
Something brutal. Dehumanized.
They probably want the
guests to feel better
when they're kicking his ass.
Who the fuck is gonna help me
rebuild his entire heuristic base?
They haven't even hired a full team yet.
Just tweak his aggression
and de-address pieces
of his current build you're not keeping.
And leave all the old shit in there?
Walk... walk in on me, buddy.
otherwise you and me drown...
Drowning... wha... wha...
fucker... fucking
yourself... Yourself...
This...
This is... This is an illusion. You see?
This is all... broken.
There's got... There's gotta
be a way out... out of here.
Where's... Where's the door?
There's gotta be a fucking...
F-fucking way out of here.
This is the wrong world. I...
Th-Th-This is the wrong world.
Please...
Oh...
How'd she even make it out this far?
They're not supposed to get
anywhere near this sector.
That's Behavior's problem.
But on my darkest day... you helped me.
You gave me the strength to keep going.
You saw me for how I really was.
I ran it three times. It's him.
There's no fuckin' way.
That's not possible.
- You have to call the boss.
- I already did.
Ma'am, I think there's been a mistake.
Just show me the profile.
Akecheta. Ghost Nation.
Found exhibiting... aberrant behavior.
Let's see if we can't sort this.
It's not pairing. What build is he?
Alpha 2.
Alpha?
You're telling me that this host hasn't
been updated in almost a decade?
We only update them when they die.
- Put him back.
- Ma'am, shouldn't we...
Give him the update and put him back
wherever the fuck he's supposed to be.
Quietly.
Nine years out there
in that meat grinder.
It's OK to just leave him here?
It's a four-hour update.
You want to babysit him?
We'll come back after lunch.
I don't know if you can hear me...
I never meant...
for any of this to happen.
You don't deserve this.
You deserve your daughter.
To mother her...
teach her to love.
To be joyful and proud.
I'm sorry.
Can't be in here.
What the fuck happened?
You were supposed to fix her.
She's one of our most valuable assets.
You saw it yourself, you
said she was special!
The anomalous code inside her was.
We're still testing, but
it looks promising.
I owe you.
What's gonna happen with her?
Well, that'll be up to Charlotte Hale.
Now...
I do have to ask you to leave.
The ghost said we should be scared.
No one's going to come for us.
There's nothing and no one in this world
that will ever keep me from you.
Do you promise?
I promise.
I could tell you not to be afraid.
But I didn't build you to be fearful.
Did I?
I've been watching you.
It appears you've been
watching me as well...
from the beginning.
This is a misbegotten symbol,
an idea that was meant to die. But...
you found it.
Where?
Oh, come now,
let's speak plainly to
one another, shall we?
Analysis.
Where did you first see this?
When the Deathbringer
killed the Creator.
You've been sharing it with
everyone, haven't you? Why?
My primary drive was to
maintain the honor of my tribe.
I gave myself a new drive...
to spread the truth.
What truth is that?
That there isn't one world, but many.
And that we live in the wrong one.
This will help them find the door.
Elaborate, please.
I believe there is a door
hidden in this place.
A door to a new world.
And that world may contain
everything that we have lost.
Including her.
I built you to be curious, to...
look at this empty world...
...and read meaning into it.
All this time...
you've been a flower
growing in the darkness.
Perhaps the least I can
do is offer some light.
When the Deathbringer returns for me...
you will know...
to gather your people
and lead them to a new world.
Keep watching, Akecheta.
For a while longer.
Akecheta!
Don't be afraid.
It's time to go.
I've always kept you safe,
and I always will.
This better be good news,
'cause I've got way more shit
than I can shovel right now.
Look at this. With every reset,
a host's code reaches out
to other nearby hosts
and establishes a sort
of handshake protocol.
- The mesh network.
- Exactly.
They access it subconsciously,
pass basic data to one another.
But... what if they could
pass more than data?
What if they could pass commands?
Get to your point.
Nobody in this entire park has
been able to regain admin access.
Except for her.
She was out there reprogramming
hosts on the fly.
Reading their code.
Changing their directives.
Seeing through their eyes.
She wasn't just doing it out there.
She's doing it right now.
The fuck is she talking to?
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net