Last year, my wife took the wrong pills.
I tried to console my daughter,
she told me that my wife's
death was no accident.
That she killed herself.
Are we logging records
of guest's experiences and their DNA?
We're not having that
conversation, Bernard.
The investment here is in the future.
I'm not interested in the future,
I'm interested in reality.
And I think in twenty
years, this will be
the only reality that matters.
Maybe so, but I'll be long gone by then.
This a retirement party? Looks
more like a coronation.
Our arrangement's been a perfect fit,
you stepping down
doesn't help me at all.
Nor me.
I was told I might...
I might not have to.
Things are progressing, but we
all need a little patience.
Yeah, well, some of us
can afford to have more
patience than others.
You don't know, do you?
The real purpose of this place?
But I do.
And one fine day,
perhaps we, actually,
resurrect the dead.
Call forth Lazarus from his cave.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Hmm.
You have a visitor, Mr. Delos.
Shall I send him in?
'Bout time.
William, m'boy.
Where the hell have you been?
It's good to see you again, Jim.
Thank fuck for that.
Most potent thing these
cretins'll give me
is grapefruit juice.
It's a little early for me.
A little fuckin' late, you mean.
Besides, if you aim to cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
So...
when can I get out of here?
Soon.
The observation period is almost over,
and the last step is a
baseline interview.
It's, uh, it's a conversation
that'll give 'em something
to refer back to.
All right. Well, let's get on with it!
This is the interview.
The thinking is, it should be conducted
by someone that's familiar to you,
a friendly face.
It's about capturing your frame of mind,
your mood, your sense of humor.
I own a biotechnology company,
and I'm dying of a
disease whose research
I defunded 15 years ago.
I think my sense of humor
is fuckin' intact.
My patience, on the other hand...
Fair enough.
I'm gonna ask you a couple of questions.
Do you know where you are?
Carlsbad, California,
in some office park I'm
probably overpaying for,
along with the rest of
this fucking endeavor.
And how long you been here?
Far too fuckin' long already.
I've got a business to run.
What is the purpose of these questions?
Like I said, they're just
trying to establish a baseline.
For what?!
Fidelity.
So, what's the idea?
That afterwards you and I have
the exact same conversation?
It seems a little far-fetched,
doesn't it, William?
No whiskey, no tobacco, low on ammo...
Wherever it is you're takin' me,
we best get there soon.
Let me go! No!
What are you doing?!
These tracks are supposed to head north,
not west.
Seems like Ford's game
has multiple contenders.
Plus it detours through Las Mudas.
What, that two-bit town? There
are better places to...
Oh, cut the crap, Lawrence.
I know you have family there.
Looks like Ford's arranging a reunion.
Clementine.
Where are we?
Hello?
Who's there?
Elsie?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Stay the hell away from me.
You're OK...
Don't move.
I'm not gonna hurt you, Else.
It's too late for that, asshole.
You choked me out and you left me here
with a bunch of fuckin'
protein bars and a bucket.
It wasn't me.
It was Ford. He forced me.
Oh, he forced you?
You knew too much.
He couldn't risk you stopping him.
Stopping him from what?
Ford wrote a g-game,
and we're all in it.
Now all the hosts are free,
with no constraints,
n-n-no safeguards.
What are you talking about?
P-Please. Please.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Please. P-P-Please.
Elsie, please.
Please.
No. Hey.
Elsie, p-p-please.
T-T-Tablet.
Cognitive... l-l-lock.
But you...
You rotated out.
Where did you go when you rotated out?
You have a family. You have an ex-wife.
You have...
a backstory.
Shh... Shh...
Shutting... down.
- Shh... Shh...
- OK. OK.
I can... I can detask your systems,
put you in safe mode.
And don't worry.
I'm not gonna brick you, asshole.
Not yet. You got too
much shit to answer for.
OK. You're gonna be out
in three...
two...
one.
Is this now?
You have extensive cortical damage.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you shot yourself.
I altered your code to ignore
the physical damage for now,
but you're not gonna last
long without cortical fluid.
With any luck,
you'll survive till they
call in the cavalry.
Elsie, wait!
Elsie.
Wait.
No one's coming for any of us.
- Delos doesn't want them to.
- What? Why?
There's something here.
Something they've been
working on a long time.
Delos won't call in the rescue
until they've ensured it's safe.
Elsie, please.
I won't last without cortical fluid.
Even if I wanted to,
we don't have any tools.
We're in Sector 22. I mean, there's
nothing out here for miles.
Bernard?
What the hell are you looking at?
Bernard. What the hell
is wrong with you?
There's a facility here.
- What?
- I think Ford
had Clementine bring
me here for a reason.
I told you, there's...
There's really nothing
around here for miles.
It's hidden.
It's part of their project.
What the hell is that?
Where does that go, Bernard?
I don't remember.
It's a whole lab.
What the hell happened here?
Oh, my God.
This is a control unit printer.
What are they doing with this?
Bernard.
What the fuck is that?
Don't threaten it and it won't hurt you.
What the hell were they doing here?
I think they were watching the guests.
What would they want with the guests?
Great. Cortical fluid.
OK.
Please.
Bernard.
Did you have something
to do with this project?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Is Ford in control of you now?
Ford's dead.
Fuck me.
OK.
OK, stay with me, Bernard.
Stay with me.
This is gonna hurt.
This can't be happening because
none of this is real, right?
It's gonna be OK. Someone'll rescue us.
Seems to me like our rescue's
in the same boat we are.
Unhh!
She said "time is coming,"
or something "is coming."
You've spent enough time in the park
to learn the language?
A lot of people tend to
ignore their narratives.
I don't like other people very much.
I've been watching 'em since
they ambushed me, and...
they keep the humans close,
but they're not killin'
us... just the hosts.
No offense, but I'm not gonna
stick around to test that theory.
Safer to wait for the first responders.
There's a protocol for evacuation.
They'll get you out of here.
Thanks.
But, uh...
I'm not looking to get out of here.
Home, sweet home, Lawrence.
Where the hell is everybody?
Whiskey.
Nothin' fancy.
You don't seem too happy
to be home, Lawrence.
I've never been the domestic type.
By some fluke of nature I got
myself a wife and a daughter
who think I hung the moon.
Truth is, I'm a son of a bitch.
Kindest thing I ever
did was to keep away.
The Gran Reserva. Only for our
most distinguished guest.
Hey, hey, hey.
I haven't even shot anybody yet.
What's your problem?
You harbor even the faintest
ambition of using that thing
and I'll turn that pretty
face of yours inside-out.
Someone took a chunk out of you boys.
What happened to the rest of you?
Double-crossed...
by some bitch name of Wyatt.
- Good for her.
- On your feet.
Go on. In here.
Papa!
Ah, mija.
Now, me and my men here
have a long journey ahead of us.
Mm.
We need food, whiskey,
and ammunition.
You people have some village elder
who can speak for you?
Make some kind of a deal?
I ain't interested in
makin' fuckin' deals.
You understand?
We know you motherfuckers are rebels.
So you're gonna tell me where the fuck
you hid your weapons,
or you're gonna die.
The second we tell him
he's gonna kill us all anyway.
They got my family.
My daughter.
You told me you had a daughter.
Did I?
I don't know. At some point.
You ain't exactly forthcoming...
but I remember that much.
The point is,
you think she'd want to watch you
gunned down in front of her?
Probably.
Well, I'm not gonna fuckin' die here.
We just need to get the weapons.
You know where they are?
They're in an unmarked grave out back.
We'll wait till they're drunk,
make a run for it.
Sound like a plan?
Yeah.
What the fuck are you doin'?
You.
Let's make a deal.
The weapons are in an unmarked
grave behind the church.
For a man who wants to deal, you
ain't very proficient at it.
Supposed to set the terms
before you give up what you got.
That's not what I'm offering.
Hmm.
I know something you don't.
I know where you're goin'.
You've been telling your men you know...
but you don't.
Just someplace you think
your dreams are comin' true
and you call it Glory, but...
it's got a lot of names.
And I know the way.
Go check the graveyard.
You have a visitor, sir.
'Bout time.
William, m'boy.
Where the hell have you been?
It's good to see you again, Jim.
A little early for me.
A little fuckin' late, you mean.
Besides, you aim to cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
Ahh.
What is the purpose of these questions?
Like I said, they're just trying
to establish a baseline.
For what?
Fidelity.
So... what's the idea?
That afterwards,
we'd have the exact same conversation?
Seems a a little far-fetched,
doesn't it, William?
It did... at first.
And here I thought...
you were just pissin' away my money.
You little fucking chancer.
I take it I didn't recover.
I'm afraid not.
How long's it been?
Seven years.
Give or take.
I'm not in California anymore, am I?
If you can't tell, does it matter?
So...
let's get me the fuck out of here!
I am ready...
to smoke my cigars,
sail my boat, fuck my wife.
I take it that last
part isn't an option.
I'm afraid not.
What did her in?
It was a stroke.
Juliet had her buried
in the family plot.
Juliet. You're lookin' after her?
Yeah.
And my granddaughter, she... she...
She's whip-smart.
- Capable.
- Ouff.
I assume my house is ready for me?
I'm afraid it's not that...
simple, Jim. We...
We're gonna need to keep you
here just a little bit longer.
OK? For some observation.
These fuckers have poked and
prodded me ad infinitum.
Yeah, but we don't want to rush it.
We don't want to wear you out.
Wear me out? I feel fuckin' brand-new.
I am ready to get out there
and see the sun.
Get some fresh aid...
Air.
Get some...
Get back to...
Mmm...
I'll come back tomorrow.
Hmmp.
You come...
Yeah.
In the...
It's good to have you back, Jim.
Same problems as before.
Made it to Day 7 this time,
so... that's progress.
Would you like to go ahead
and terminate, sir?
Go ahead.
Whew.
Great-lookin' piece.
Got stolen at the border.
Ain't that right, amigo?
Hmm. Nitro.
Whoo! Oh, boy!
We are going to blast
our way clear to Glory.
- What the...
- Ahh.
Sorry. So sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey. You need steadier
hands in your occupation.
Let me teach you.
Now, how 'bout you try and
measure a dozen paces?
Well done, my friend.
_
Ai! Ai!
Oh, God. It's too late.
You and your stupid fucking fantasy.
You've gotten us killed.
You live only as long as the
last person who remembers you.
Elsie.
Pint or so of the good stuff.
You should be feeling a
bit more like yourself.
Thank you.
I still don't trust you.
I also figure I might need your help.
Whoever did this really didn't want us
accessing whatever's on this processor.
It's an entirely different
OS than our systems.
A language I've never seen.
I've seen this kind of
encryption scheme before.
Where?
In Peter Abernathy's head.
In reference to a database much larger
than anything I know of in the park.
I think I've been here before.
- Can you remember?
- I think Ford sent me here.
I'm not sure.
The damage is repaired,
but my memories, I...
I get lost in them.
I can't tell if this is now or then.
Yeah. I saw that when I was
digging around in your code.
Your memories aren't addressed.
They're just kind of
drifting around in there,
so when you're experiencing
one, you have no idea
whether it comes before
or after the others.
I've been here recently.
Why?
What were you doing?
I don't know...
but I think I know what
they were doing here.
They weren't building hosts...
Not exactly.
What were they building
here, if not hosts?
The same hardware,
but the code is different,
the language...
Not code at all, not really.
Elsie.
Don't.
Whatever they're making here,
it's behind this door.
Maybe we don't want to know.
We have to see what's inside.
Elsie.
I'm not here with you, am I?
I'm trying to remember.
I'm trying to remember
what we found here.
It wasn't hosts they were making.
It was something else.
Elsie, don't!
If you wanted this nitro,
you didn't have to steal it.
Open up!
No?
Keep fuckin' playin'.
There ya go.
Ahhh.
You look restless.
Are you upset the way we're
treatin' your friend?
He's not my friend,
and we're wasting time.
I've known men like you.
All the death... makes you agitated.
Don't worry.
Me and death...
we go way back.
Come over here...
mamacita.
Death...
is an old... amigo of mine.
I died just recently, in fact.
But death can't bear to lay claim on me.
So it sent me back here...
to do its bidding.
Because I...
I do it with such goddamn style.
Your husband looks parched, huh?
Let's get him a drink. What do you say?
Mmm.
Nice and slow, ya hear?
No...
I've served death well.
And in turn,
it'll be watching over us
as we cross these lands.
You think death favors you,
that it brought you back.
But death's decisions are final.
It's only the living that...
That are inconstant... and waver,
don't know who they are
or what they want.
Death is always true.
You haven't known a true
thing in all your life.
You think you know death...
but you don't.
Is that so?
You didn't recognize him sittin'
across from you this whole time.
Open up.
Don't worry, amigo.
I'm here now...
watching over you.
I believe you said this was yours.
You have a visitor, sir.
Shall I send him in?
'Bout time.
Who the fuck are you?
Been a long time, Jim.
Good to see you again.
William?
William, my boy.
Well, fuck me.
I take it I didn't recover.
I'm afraid not.
How ya feelin'?
Better than you look.
And speaking of things that age well...
Well, thank fuck for that.
Most potent thing these
cretins will give me
is grapefruit juice.
Little early for me.
Little too fuckin' late, you mean.
Besides, you cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
Ahh.
Whew.
So...
how long has it been?
Longer than we thought.
So then, let's get me
the fuck outta here!
No, I don't think so.
Why?
I'm as fit as a fi...
I'm as...
You're feeling it more. Aren't you?
The engineers call it
a cognitive plateau.
Your mind is stable for
a few hours, few days,
and then it starts to fall apart.
Every time.
At first we thought it was your
mind rejecting the new body.
Like an organ that's
not a perfect match.
But it's more like your mind...
rejects reality.
Rejects itself.
I don't, uh...
'member any prior...
I... I...
I...
Attemp...
No, Jim, this is the 149th
time we've brought you back.
We're gettin' closer to
workin' out the kinks,
slowly but surely.
You're on Day 35.
You're only now starting to degrade.
I feel... fuckin' fi...
Ticker...
Steady as a...
'ru...
Another year or two,
they might crack it...
- 'ru... 'ru...
- And get a version of you
that's viable long-term.
But the thing is...
I'm not so sure anymore.
I'm beginning to think
that this whole enterprise
was a mistake.
People aren't meant to live forever.
I mean, take you, for example.
Ruthless philanderer
with no ethics in your
business or family dealings,
a veritable shithead.
In truth...
everyone prefers the memory
of you to the man himself.
Want me to stay here forever, do ya?
Hmm?
Enjoyin'...
running my company, Bill?
Livin' in my house?
Fucking my daughter? Hmm?
Juliet's dead.
She killed herself.
Why would she...
Why would she do that?
What did you...
What did you do to her?
World is better off without you, Jim.
Possibly without me.
Logan!
Logan overdosed years ago.
Couldn't face reality, either.
Your wife's gone, Juliet's gone...
no one's coming to help you.
Took me a long time to learn this...
but some men are better off dead.
Good night, Jim.
I don't understand. He was stable.
We should terminate, sir.
- Sir!
- Leave him.
Might be useful to
observe his degradation
over the next few days.
- Elsie.
- Someone's in there.
Hello?
I'm all the way down now.
I can see all the way to the bottom.
You like to see what I see?
Stay away.
Ohh!
Oh...
They said there were two fathers.
One above, one below.
They lied.
There was only ever the devil.
And when you look up from the bottom,
it was just his reflection...
laughing back down at you.
You aim to cheat the devil...
you owe him at least an offering.
Save your bullets.
I'll put him out of his misery.
Tell me that was a host and not a human.
I think it was both.
That... person
was James Delos.
I thought he died years ago.
He did.
So they printed his body...
and they copied his developed
mind onto a control unit,
like our hosts.
And by the looks of it, unsuccessfully.
But I think they intend to keep trying.
Fuck that.
They're gonna get us all killed
so some asshole can live forever?
No.
I gotta get to the Mesa.
I'm gonna contact the mainland.
Fuck Ford and his game.
And fuck these assholes
and their project.
Wait.
I think I know why Ford sent me here.
He had me print a control
unit for someone else.
Another human.
Who?
I don't know.
But I need to find out.
We'll go together. I can help you.
Elsie.
The things I did before...
I wasn't in control.
But since Ford died, that's all changed.
For the first time, I get
to decide who I want to be.
Please.
Give me that chance.
Fuck it.
I always trusted code
more than people anyway.
But you gotta promise me one thing.
No more lies. OK?
And you'll never hurt me again.
Of course.
OK.
Help me...
please.
Is everything OK?
Everything's fine.
Gracias.
You said we need some men.
My cousins want to help
us on our journey west.
Figure they'd follow you
anywhere out of gratitude.
Well, let's not get
carried away, Lawrence.
Most of 'em won't be comin' back.
They might not remember...
but I know who you are, William.
One good deed doesn't change that.
Who said anything about a good deed?
You wanted me to play your game.
I'm gonna play it to the bone.
And you still don't understand the
real game we're playing here.
If you're looking forward, you're
looking in the wrong direction.
Papa!
Yah! Yah!
Hi, Dad.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net