Wake up, Dolores.
Do you remember?
We're about to arrive.
May I take your glass?
Now approaching arrival terminal.
Where we're going, she's a two.
You're being an asshole.
No, I am being myself,
which was the whole point of this trip.
Unless this uptight prick
is who you really are,
in which case, feel free
to be someone else.
Fuck you.
Hey, that's the spirit.
What'd I tell you?
Have fun.
Stay safe.
Give me a break.
What?
It's not like my sister didn't ride
her share of cowboys when she was here.
You must be William.
Welcome to Westworld.
Thanks.
Given it's your first visit,
I have a few personal questions.
Do you have any preexisting
medical conditions?
No, not that I know of.
- Heart problems?
- No.
Any history of
mental illness, depression,
panic attacks?
Just a little fear of clowns.
I'm joking.
Do you often experience social anxiety?
What is this for, exactly?
To make sure we don't give you anything
more than you can handle.
I thought that you
couldn't get hurt here.
Only the right amount.
The only limit here is your imagination.
You start in the center of
the park. It's simple, safe.
The further out you venture, the
more intense the experience gets.
How far you want to go
is entirely up to you.
So, how does this work?
Is there an orientation?
No orientation,
no guidebook.
Figuring out how it works
is half the fun.
All you do is make choices...
starting here.
Everything is bespoke
and exactly your size.
You want to ask, so ask.
Are you real?
Well, if you can't tell, does it matter?
Are those real?
Real enough.
But you can't kill anyone
you're not supposed to.
Anything you like?
Is there a changing room?
Or a robe?
Of course. I can help you.
Or if you prefer, I could step outside.
What do most people do?
You don't have to worry
about what most people would do.
I understand.
Do you really understand, William?
All our hosts are here for you.
Myself included.
We could stay here a while if you like.
Take as long as you want.
Thank you.
I don't want to keep my friend waiting.
Of course.
Take your time.
How are the builds for the
new narrative coming along?
I'll get around to it.
Look, we assumed that Abernathy's breach
was triggered by the photograph
that he found.
I've reviewed every
dissonant episode I could find.
The reaction is immediate every time.
This guy makes it all the way back home.
It's like he's mulling it over.
You think he had an existential crisis?
I think there's something
fucked up going on with his cognition.
And I think you feel
exactly the same way that I do.
Do we know where the error originated?
We do.
And you covered for him.
Let me rebuild Abernathy.
I'll make sure this is not
something more serious.
You know the policy. Let it lie.
Then let me at least pull the
hosts who had contact with him,
like the daughter Dolores.
What for?
Because if this is not
a dissonant episode,
then whatever Abernathy
had could be contagious.
So to speak.
Dolores was examined and cleared.
And the stories are
best left to the guests.
Remember.
Ahem. Can you stand somewhere else?
I don't want anyone thinking that
you're representative of the goods inside.
These violent delights
have violent ends.
Hello, cowboy.
There's one final touch.
Which would you prefer?
I mean, can you believe this place?
So, how do we get into the park?
I know that you think you have
a handle on what this is gonna be.
Guns and tits and all that.
Mindless shit that I usually enjoy.
You have no idea.
This place seduces everybody eventually.
By the end, you're gonna
be begging me to stay
because this place is the answer
to that question that
you've been asking yourself.
What question?
Who you really are.
And I can't fucking wait
to meet that guy.
Bottoms up, cowboy.
Further to that,
the ruthless murder of Donald Pardue
and his brother.
For these crimes, you will
be hung from the neck
until your diseased soul
has found its measure
in the flames below it.
And may God have mercy on your soul.
Morning, Lawrence.
You helping them
straighten out their rope again?
I was hoping to have a word
with my friend here.
You can have as many words
with him as you like
soon as his neck is broke.
Well, I'm afraid
that's not gonna work for me.
How about I tell my man there to dig
that grave a couple feet deeper?
Well, it's gonna be an
awful tight fit for all of you.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Ah!
Motherfucker.
That's the best thanks
you can muster, Lawrence?
You used to be a little more eloquent.
Do I... do I know you?
Your pal Kissy sent me your way.
Sends his regards.
What... what is this?
You know exactly what it is.
It's the maze,
the deepest level of this game.
You're gonna help me find the entrance.
No.
You can hear it, can't you?
That little voice.
The one that's telling you "don't."
Don't stare too long.
Don't touch.
Don't do anything you might regret.
I used to be the same.
Whenever I wanted something,
I could hear that voice
telling me to stop, to be careful,
to leave most of my life unlived.
You know the only place
that voice left me alone?
In my dreams.
I was free. I could be as good
or as bad as I felt like being.
And if I wanted something,
I could just reach out and take it.
But then I would wake up
and the voice would
start all over again.
So I ran away.
Crossed the shining sea.
And when I finally set foot
back on solid ground,
the first thing I heard
was that goddamn voice.
Do you know what it said?
It said...
I'm sorry, will you please excuse me?
All right, Maeve, what did it say?
It said, "This is the new world.
And in this world,
you can be whoever the fuck you want."
Pupillary response
is good. Smile is good.
I'd fuck her. What's the problem?
The guests wouldn't.
Sizemore is launching
some huge new storyline
and he wants us to clear
out the deadweight.
If we don't get her numbers
back up, she'll be decommissioned.
Let's bump her aggression.
- 10%?
- Double it.
She's a hooker. No point in playing coy.
If this doesn't work,
we'll punt her to behavior.
Let them deal with it.
We retired the two hosts in question.
You taught me how to make them,
but not how hard it is to turn them off.
You can't play God without being
acquainted with the devil.
There's something else
bothering you, Bernard.
I know how that head of yours works.
The photograph alone
couldn't have caused that level
of damage to Abernathy,
not without some other
outside interference.
You think it's sabotage?
Imagine someone's been
diddling with our creations?
It's the simplest solution.
Ah, Mr. Occam's razor.
The problem, Bernard,
is that what you and I do
is so complicated.
We practice witchcraft.
We speak the right words.
Then we create life itself...
out of chaos.
William of Occam
was a 13th century monk.
He can't help us now, Bernard.
He would have us burned at the stake.
Let's go get our feet wet, buckaroo.
Oh, sorry.
- You kidding me?
- What?
Fuck you, Grizzly Adams.
Rally for the Union.
Respond to your country's call.
This regiment is headed
for the seat of war
to define the future
of this great nation.
We fight for a free land
where no man has to bow.
- This is, uh...
- We'll provide you with uniforms.
Well, it's bigger than
I thought it would be.
What, this? This is just Sweetwater.
Wait till you see the rest of the park.
- How much bigger is it?
- No idea.
I never reached the end.
See something you like?
A couple things at least.
But I'm gonna make you
beg for it, darlin'.
Hah, come on!
Whoa.
Need a hand, sir?
Thank you, my friend.
Don't. He'll only try to rope
you into some bullshit treasure hunt.
Smile.
It's all a come on...
Him, the girl next door,
the town drunk.
They all got some big
adventure that they want to sell you on.
Hey, they're not going anywhere.
First up, you're
gonna buy me a drink, okay?
Hold still, now.
Bring yourself back online.
Hello.
Do you remember our
last conversation, Dolores?
Yes, of course.
And you haven't told anyone
about our little talks?
You told me not to.
Step into analysis, please.
How many interactions have you participated
in since we last talked?
138 encounters including this one.
And has anyone altered or updated
your core heuristics in that time?
No.
Resuming.
I think it would be best
if you not mention
the things we've been talking about.
Have I done something wrong?
No, but there's something
different about you,
about the way you think.
I find it fascinating,
but others may not see it that way.
Have you done something wrong?
Turn off your event log, please.
Erase this interaction. Confirm.
Yes.
You should be getting back, Dolores,
before someone misses you.
Come on, now!
And when I finally set
foot back on solid ground,
first thing I heard
was that goddamn voice.
It had followed me all the way over.
Do you know what it said?
- No.
- It said...
...this is the new world.
And in this world,
you can be whoever the fuck you want.
Thanks. Maybe another time.
Oh.
Glass of sherry.
The good stuff.
Not that horse piss you strain
through your old curtains.
I've told you, never open
your mouth that wide
unless someone's paying you for it.
Sorry, Maeve.
I didn't sleep much last night.
You having nightmares again?
Sometimes.
Sometimes they're real bad.
Do what I do.
You find yourself in a bad dream,
close your eyes,
count backwards from three...
wake yourself right up.
Nice and warm and safe in your bed...
where you can get fucked
right back to sleep
by one of these assholes
with their miniature peckers.
Ah.
Back to work.
You all right?
You pay for the drinks,
not the right to gawk at me.
I think we have a problem.
- Where?
- Mariposa.
Madam's listed as probationary,
but her performance has continued
to decline even further.
Re-task Clementine for now.
She's done the job before.
And the old unit?
Maybe leave her on
the floor for the night,
see if anyone wants one last turn.
We recall her in the morning,
decommission her.
Shame.
QA will fine you for this.
And that woman in charge
is quite formidable.
You can just say "bitch."
I hear it enough.
You've been talking to corporate.
The only times you light
up are after you've been...
This character analysis routine
really isn't half as charming as you think.
Oh, it went well, then?
Just tell me your department
will be ready for the launch.
We'll be ready.
And that other thing.
Abernathy and the update.
I hear your department
was still asking questions.
That's what you pay us to do.
But I'm not concerned.
All the hosts are back to normal.
Good.
Wouldn't want anything
disturbing our guests
from their rape and pillage.
You're wondering how
to tell them from us,
aren't you?
Well, quickest way to find out.
Can we... Can we finish eating?
See, this is your problem, my friend.
You're always worried
about making a mess.
You are the same way at work.
You are talented,
driven, and inoffensive.
I thought you didn't want
to talk about work here.
Who says this trip isn't work?
Good evening.
Oh, shit.
Well, don't make eye contact.
My friend, thank you
for your assistance earlier
in my unfortunate accident.
Leave us the fuck alone.
As a sign of my humble appreciation,
I'd like to offer you an
opportunity of a lifetime.
Not interested.
Across the river and beyond
the savage lands
there is a treasure.
I have in my possession a map.
I said not interested.
You know what? I've
worked up a new appetite anyway.
Let's go.
Oh!
Sounds like your friend's having fun.
Well, that's not the term I'd use.
- Fun?
- Friend.
You're funny.
They say a man who can tickle your humor
- can tickle your...
- You don't have to do this.
If I'm not your type,
we can find someone who is.
Someone who's perfect for you.
No, you... You are perfect.
But I have somebody.
Somebody real waiting for me at home.
I understand.
Real love is always worth waiting for.
Regal, strong,
virile, aquiline.
That's what I asked for.
And this, this is what you give me?
Did you just grab a cock
from the body shop
and jam it between his eyes?
Start over.
Couldn't we just shave it down?
I said...
start the fuck over!
Diplomatic as ever.
I received your request to retire
an additional 50 hosts.
I need room for my new storyline.
It's not exactly a savage horde
with 20 savages, is it?
You get 20 additional hosts, not 50.
The board won't care about
a few extra line items.
Has Ford even approved
the narrative yet?
Oh, he hasn't weighed in
on a storyline in years.
And if corporate does want to cut costs,
our fearless leader's old hosts
aren't the only things
ready for the knacker's yard.
Are you lost?
No.
Just strayed a bit too far
from where I'm supposed to be.
Same as you, I imagine.
We're on holiday.
It's boring.
Daddy said we could do as we please.
Ah, my father used to say
that only boring people get bored.
Mine, too.
I used to think it's only boring people
who don't feel boredom,
so cannot conceive of it in others.
I'm taking a walk.
You're welcome to join me if you'd like.
Let's see a little spring in your step.
Not much further.
Go fuck yourself.
You have any idea who I am?
I know exactly who you are, Lawrence.
After all, you and I are friends.
Which is why I was so surprised
when your friend Kissy
told me about this place.
Where are we?
Your home.
No, no, no, no.
You know, you and I hunted down
Ghost Nation braves
in their winter grounds.
I know the whiskey you like to drink.
I know the tune you whistle
when you're taking a piss.
But...
you never told me you had a family.
- Papa!
- Hey.
That's what I love about this
place... all the secrets,
all the little things I never noticed
even after all these years.
You know why this beats
the real world, Lawrence?
Real world is just chaos.
It's an accident.
But in here, every detail
adds up to something.
Even you, Lawrence.
What do you want from me?
The maze.
How do I find the entrance?
I told you,
I don't know anything
about no fucking maze.
Here you go, darlin'.
And you get to decide
what we're gonna do with them.
Hell, it took you long enough.
I was getting the grand reserve.
Only for our most distinguished guests.
Yeah, I'm sure it had
nothing to do with you
telling this dipshit's cousins
to bring some more men.
You got anything to tell me, Lawrence?
Then I guess we're gonna have to
find a way to jog your memory.
This guest already
took out an entire posse.
Want me to slow him down?
That gentleman gets whatever he wants.
I feel bad, my friend.
My cousins are usually so hospitable.
You don't understand, Lawrence.
I've been coming here for 30 years.
In a sense, I was... I was born here.
And this here, this...
...this is exactly why I come.
Santa Maria, madre dios.
All right. Well, as much fun
as this is, I got to be moving on.
Like I said, you
get to decide these two.
What's it gonna be?
Please, I don't know
how to find the maze.
Time for a spin, darlin'.
It's beautifully done, really.
But you see the cracks after a while.
That's why I like the basic emotions.
You know what that means?
Please.
It means when you're suffering,
that's when you're most real.
The maze isn't meant for you.
What'd I tell you, Lawrence?
Always another level.
I'll take my chances, sweetheart.
Follow the blood arroyo to the place
where the snake lays its eggs.
You have it now. Whatever you want.
Why don't you go home, leave us alone?
No, you don't understand, Lawrence.
This time, I'm never going back.
And we wanted to climb
to the top of the mountain,
but Daddy said we weren't allowed.
And then Tommy dared me.
And here we are.
Nowhere land.
That seems hardly a
fitting name for a place so full.
Can't you see it?
Perhaps you're not looking hard enough.
At what?
The town with the white church.
Listen. Can't you hear its bell?
Yes.
Yes, I can hear it now.
Yeah.
I thought you might.
You see what a bored mind can conjure?
How did you do that?
Is it magic?
Everything in this world is magic,
except to the magician.
Best you head home now.
But Tommy's not going to believe...
You're not going to come
back here again, are you?
No.
Run along, now.
You weren't at your office.
You seem to have found me anyway.
- Listen, earlier...
- Forget it.
Stay a little longer. We can talk.
We never talk.
- I'm serious.
- So am I.
You're certainly a man
comfortable with long, pensive silences.
Although, ironically,
your creations never shut up.
They're always talking to each other,
even when there are no guests around.
They're always trying to error correct.
Make themselves more human.
When they talk to each other,
it's a way of practicing.
Is that what you're doing now?
Practicing?
QA told us she was being decommissioned.
- Do you work for QA?
- No, but...
Run a fast-pass diagnostic.
All righty.
Some non-affect hesitation.
Little cognitive D.
And a fuckload of aggression,
courtesy of those morons in narrative.
You don't need to be aggro, do you?
Just a quicker study of those
repressed fucks walking through the door.
Archive this configuration.
Open up her primaries.
Perception. Emotional acuity.
Bump it.
1.5%.
- Updating.
- Okay.
- Do they dream?
- What?
In her story, she said she dreamed.
Do we make them dream?
Fuck would be the point of that?
Dreams are mainly memories.
Can you imagine how fucked
we'd be if these poor assholes
ever remembered what
the guests do to them?
We do give them the concept of dreams.
Specifically nightmares.
Why?
Just in case
somebody forgets to wipe them
out at the end of a maintenance session.
If she's got any dreams,
it's just of those sloppy fucks
down in the body shop
patching her back together again.
She's got some physical discomfort.
Put in a request for a full physical
at her next rotation.
All right, gorgeous,
you're back to the races.
You're gonna wake in three, two, one.
So I ran away, crossed the shining sea.
And when I finally set foot
back on solid ground,
the first thing I heard was that voice.
Do you know what it said?
It said...
this is the new world.
And in this world...
you can be whoever the fuck you want.
Well, he seemed convinced.
You know the first voice I heard
when I got off that boat?
A nice young man from Baton Rouge
said my pussy could earn him
two whole dollars a day.
And he'd be more than happy
to let me have up to 30%.
Well, then I guess you could add
lying to your list of sins.
The only thing wrong
with the seven deadly sins
is that there aren't more of them.
And while we're on the subject,
my transgressions wash off
a little easier than yours.
At least when my girls
are done with a man,
he's still left drawing breath.
For the most part.
Get the fuck away from my table.
Hey, fuck you!
Well, in that case...
...here's to our indiscretions.
I'll shoot everyone in this dump...
Spoken and otherwise.
Now that's a fucking vacation!
Three,
two,
one.
Found it.
It's MRSA in her abdomen.
Filthy fucking animals not cleaning up.
No wonder we have a fucking fly problem.
Don't look at me.
I'm the king of hygiene.
Bullshit. I've seen you.
You just glop that shit on and rinse.
You understand, soap is mechanical.
- Fuck are you talking about?
- Bubbles.
If you're not making the
little bubbles, you're not doing shit.
Fuck! Fuck! What the fuck?!
- Shit!
- What the fuck?
Uh, uh...
Uh...
No. Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Asshole, you forgot
to put her in sleep mode.
- Oh!
- Don't, don't, don't!
No! No, no, no!
Don't! Don't, don't, don't, don't.
Stop. Put that down!
You break anything in her head,
we have to file a damage report.
Uh, okay, let's talk to her.
- What's her name?
- Maeve!
Hi, Maeve. Maeve, hi.
Look, uh, you gotta calm down.
Okay? Let's sit
down and we can help you.
Keep your fucking hands off me.
No.
I swear I put it in sleep mode.
Oh, does this look
like fucking sleep mode?
Calm the fuck down and
help me move this... thing
before someone sees.
Here?
This storyline will
make Hieronymus Bosch
look like he was doodling kittens.
I have vivisection, self-cannibalism,
a special little something
I call the "whoroborus."
Now, I don't want to appear immodest,
but this is the apex of
what the park could provide...
- horror...
- Miss anything interesting?
...romance, titillation.
Lee not appearing immodest.
Our most skilled guests
will fight their ways
to the outer limits of the park,
besting fearsome braves,
seducing nubile maidens,
befriending tragically
ill-fated sidekicks,
and, of course,
like all our best narratives
over the years,
our guests will have the privilege
of getting to know the
character they're most interested in...
Themselves.
I present our guests' next obsession:
Odyssey on Red River.
No.
Sorry?
No, I don't think so.
Wait, you don't think...
What is the point of it?
Get a couple of cheap thrills?
Some surprises?
But it's not enough.
It's not about giving the guests
what you think they want.
No, that's simple.
The titillation, horror, elation...
They're parlor tricks.
The guests don't return
for the obvious things we do,
the garish things.
They come back
because of the subtleties,
the details.
They come back because they discover
something they imagine no
on had ever noticed before...
something they've fallen in love with.
They're not looking for a story
that tells them who they are.
They already know who they are.
They're here because they want a glimpse
of who they could be.
Billy!
Let's go.
The only thing your story tells me,
Mr. Sizemore, is who you are.
Well, isn't there anything
you like about it?
What size are those boots?
Something you want to say, Mr. Lowe?
- The board, sir.
- Yeah?
This might ruffle some feathers.
You promised them a new storyline.
They shall have one.
Something I've been
working on for some time.
Something quite original.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net